salesgossip.co.uk 2013-05-20

# Privacy Policy | SalesGossip

Sales Gossip is a free, information management service. This policy describes the types of personal information we may collect and how we use it to provide the Sales Gossip service.

By using Sales Gossip, you agree to the collection and use of your personal information as described in this policy. You should know:

  * We collect limited account information and store and maintain your account, information and events list on our secure servers.
  * We will never rent, sell or share information that personally identifies you for marketing purposes without your express permission.

You can update or delete your account information and preferences at any time.

To comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, at this time Sales Gossip is only available to users who are at least 13 years old. If you are under 13, please do not use the Sales Gossip service.

What types of personal information do we collect and how do we use it?

Account information. When you register with Sales Gossip, we will request some personal information, including your first and last name, email address and mobile number. Your password will be maintained on our system in an encrypted form.

Events & Information list contents and usage. The contents of your Sales Gossip account are stored and maintained on Sales Gossip servers in order to provide the service. Because we keep back-up copies of data for the purposes of recovery from errors or system failure, residual copies of E&I list contents may remain on our systems for some time, even after you have deleted information or after the termination of your account. Sales Gossip employees do not access the content of any task lists unless you specifically request them to do so (for example, if you are having technical difficulties accessing your account) or if required by law, to maintain our system, or to protect Sales Gossip or the public.

We also may collect information about the use of your account, such as how much storage you are using, how often you log in, who do you received information from and other information related to your registration and use of Sales Gossip. Information displayed or clicked on in your Sales Gossip account (including UI elements, links, and other information) is also recorded. We use this information internally to deliver the best possible service to you, such as improving the Sales Gossip user interface.

Sales Gossip will never sell, rent or share your personal information with any third parties for marketing purposes without your express permission.

**Cookies & log information.**

Cookies. A cookie is a small data file that is sent to your computer when you first visit a website. As with most website cookies, our cookies include an identification number that is unique to the computer you are using. This identifier helps us better understand our user base and how they are using our site and services.

When you visit Sales Gossip and create an Sales Gossip account, we set and access cookies on your computer. We use cookies for a number of reasons, such as recognising you when you visit the site, displaying the site according to your chosen user settings for language, and maintaining the security of your account. We may also use the cookies to collect aggregated information about the use of Sales Gossip to maintain, analyse and improve the service. If you set your browser so that it refuses cookies, you will not be able to use the Sales Gossip service.

Log information. When you use your Sales Gossip account, we collect certain information (the same information that most web sites log when they are accessed). This information, contained in the "header" of your request to access the Sales Gossip page, usually includes the browser type you used, your Internet Protocol address, and the date and time of day. In addition, we log the unique ID provided by our cookie and the URL of the last site you visited.

As a basic matter, we need this information to help us provide our services to you. For example, we need to validate your identity in order to maintain the security of your personal profile We also need to know what Internet Protocol address your query came from so we can send the appropriate pages back to you.

In addition, we log this information for internal business purposes. For example, this log information helps us determine how well our services are working so we can continually improve the quality of Sales Gossip. The log information is also important for security, audit, quality improvement, and other internal business purposes.

**How we may contact you.**

Sales Gossip may send you information related to your Sales Gossip account or Sales Gossip services. Because we believe such information is important, you will not be given the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them.

**Transfer of information.**

Personal information collected by Sales Gossip may be stored and processed in the United Kingdom.

We reserve the right to transfer your personal information in the event of a transfer of ownership of Sales Gossip, such as acquisition by or merger with another company. In such an event, Sales Gossip will notify you before information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

**Updating your information.**

You can terminate your account at any time, by going to the administration page. We typically deactivate accounts within two business days of such requests. You should be aware, however, that residual copies of information may remain stored on our systems even after the deletion of information or the termination of your account.

We hope you will enjoy using Sales Gossip!
